

Rajat **Tamoli**

Software Engineer

•	869695807
1	00000007

rajatyaduvanshi99@gmail.

sheetal nagar,Indore, Madhya Pradesh

https://rajaty.github.io/website/

About Me

Working as a Software Engineer and DevOps from 2.3 years in Rakuten Symphony with skills in requirements definition, release management, and code debugging and deployment on production releases with Kubernetes on 5G-RAN. Works great with technical and non-technical teams to coordinate on-time, quality releases.

Education

B.TECH Computer Science Enginnering 2015 - 2019

Global Institute Of Technology - Jaipur, RJ

Intermediate/+2 (RBSE) 2013 - 2015

Pratap Adarsh S.S.School - Jaipur, RJ

Matriculation (RBSE) 2012 - 2013

Adarsh Vidhya Mandir secondary school - Jaipur,RJ

Skills

- Docker and Kubernetes
- Java Programming
- Web development languages (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap)
- Apache Spark
- Maven and Spring Microservices with docker deployment
- Mysql

Others:

- Helm and Robin
- Harbor repo for Docker Images
- Swagger
- Git
- CI-CD Deployment
- Windows and Linux Operating Systems
- Scripting Languages shell
- Jira and Slack
- AWS (EC2, S3, ECR, CI/CD) and Telco Cloud Automation
- SonarOube

LANGUAGES

English HINDI

Work Experiences

Software Engineer At Rakuten Symphony (2020 - Present)

- Observability Framework of cloud-native applications For Dish and Rakuten for 5g:
- Observability framework (OBF) to collect telemetry data from all 5G network functions that will enable the use of process data to operate and optimize the DISH and Rakuten 5G network.
- 2. Worked on docker and k8s for deploy Microservice and Observe the framework for Monitoring and visualization on 4g/5g Network and application data used below Components:
 - ELK Stack
- Prometheus and Grafana
- Apache Kafka
- Alert-manager
- Apache Spark and Logstash (for process data)
- Fluentbit/Fileabeat etc.
- Worked on Linux Shell Script programming
- Maven Projects for Log processing.

Full Stack Developer Trainee - At JSpiders Training & Development Center (2019-2020)

 Conducted in-depth assessments into Java infrastructure with SQL Database and Frontend for design, development, and management of Java-based applications.

Personal Website

- Create a Personal website using Html, CSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap and Contains links to the project resume and contact information, and is Hosted on Github-Pages.
- Project Links: <u>https://rajaty.github.io/website/</u>

Links

- GITHUB PAGE: https://github.com/rajaty
- LINKEDIN PROFILE: https://www.linkedin.com/in/rajat-tamoli-41923a12b/